And the grand winner for
this year's science fair is...
Virus Detector of
Nicholas Javier!
[APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[NOTIFICATION CHIMES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHIMING CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA]
Bayes' Theorem is a formula
used to update the probability
of an event
based on new evidence.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SCREAMS]
[SHUTTERS CLICKING]
If I give them new information,
if I tell them my side
of the story...
will it change how they see me?
[SHUTTERS CLICKING]
I'm so tired of being judged.
Should I just let them be?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SHUTTER CLICKS]
[SONYA] I don't care!
Someone has to pay
for what happened
to my daughter, Attorney.
So, let's just file the case.
And no, we will not settle.
Let's take it to court.
I don't care if we reach
the Supreme Court.
I won't let them get away
with this.
Marla?
Do you want to talk
with the attorney?
Attorney, let's just meet, yeah.
Thank you.
[BEEPS]
Don't worry, Marla.
I will not let the school
get away with this.
Even Cole.
I know...
it's tough to take on Adolf
because of his connections,
but...
we won't back down.
We will get you justice.
[KNOCKS]
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
Oh.
Hi, girls!
Nice to see you all...
Wait...
Don't you have class today?
We're boycotting SOSH, Auntie.
Why are they suspending Marla
when it wasn't even her fault?
M-mmh.
She hasn't eaten yet.
I'll leave her to you, okay?
Okay, go on.
Thank you, Auntie.
Girl...
Marla, how are you now?
Isn't it obvious?
She's devastated.
Are you Marla?
Are you two still squabbling?
It's just our...
love language,
I guess.
You know, girl,
that school is unbelievable.
Of course, they covered it up
once more.
Especially since
Daphne's monster-in-law
seems to care more about
what the foreign delegates
think than...
your well-being.
What do you mean,
"Mother-in-law?"
I'd never,
ever get back with that
damned son of hers!
No matter how many times
she'd bribe my mom and dad,
no, never again!
We can't let them do this.
We have to get back at them.
Especially Cole.
Isobel, now is not
the right time for revenge.
You're right.
Oh, wow!
I couldn't believe it, girl.
You're agreeing with us now.
- I'm proud of you.
- But, seriously,
Marla...
how are you feeling?
I keep going back
to what happened.
It keeps...
replaying in my head.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
All I can say is
I did that...
because...
I love him.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I wanted to show him
that I trust him
and that I'm willing
to start anew.
I didn't...
ever think that...
he'd use that against me.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm smart.
Heck, I'm a fucking genius.
But I feel like the most
stupid person in the world.
Marla, don't say that.
You're not stupid.
But I did the most
stupid thing in my life.
I feel...
I feel so empty.
I feel like...
a piece of me died,
and...
I'm still grieving.
Thank you for coming.
It means a lot.
[VOICE BREAKING] I just can't...
can't go out right now.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
- Hey!
- Enough!
- Let go of me!
- Faster, you moron!
He tried to run.
Good thing I caught him.
Ant, my man!
Why so disgusted?
Didn't you like it
this way before?
Ew.
[SCOFFS]
Is it true, Ant?
That you wanted to leave
the group?
What?
Where'd you even get that?
You know I would never do that,
but seriously?
You traded me out for this?
Why did you sabotage
our science project, huh?
Why'd you sabotage it?
[HUFFS]
What are you talking about?
Where did you even hear that?
Cole, you know me
better than anyone.
You know I would never do that.
I respect hard work.
I respect technologies
that elevate
our understanding
of the universe, you know...
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BLOW LANDS]
[ANT GRUNTING IN PAIN]
You know,
you talk way too much.
You're lucky we accepted
you back
into the Kings of SOSH,
even if we know you're a fag.
Faggot.
But what did you do?
You sabotaged...
and shit all over us.
Huh?
Let me go.
Goddamn you.
Don't you ever forget,
you were the one
who asked for my help
in building
your fucking machine.
But when I was the one in need,
you all abandoned me.
And guess who was there for me
when I needed help?
It was Nyx.
So, you have no right to talk
as if you know everything.
Goddamn you.
Wait...
you're with Nyx?
Pick him up.
- Stand up.
- What the hell?!
- Stand up!
- Migo!
What the fuck?
damn you,
Please, please, please,
enough...
- please, enough.
- You fucking morons!
Enough already, please.
Please?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I said let me go!
Come on!
When will you stop, damn it?
You know what Dad taught me?
Never let anyone cross me
without making them pay.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [ANT GRUNTS]
What are you doing?
[ANT] Let me go!
What's this, Cole?
Oh!
You've got yourself a hero now?
What now?
You want me to beat him up,
too, best friend?
Wait a minute!
Stop this, please!
- Come on, guys!
- Migo, you're a fucking coward!
Someone might see us.
I'll tell on you.
- I'll report the three of you.
- To whom?
Lester's mommy?
Snitch on us, then.
I'll even go with you.
Let's go. Right now?
You're so full of yourselves
because you think you can
get away with anything.
Right, Cole?
Is that why it
was so easy for you
to leak Marla's videos?
Huh?
Video? Really?
I don't know anything
about that.
Why would I?
Besides...
I love Marla very much.
I love my girlfriend very much.
Why would you do that to her?
Can't you accept the fact
that she's ranked higher
than you?
You can't accept that a girl
is ahead of you.
You're so desperate.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's see who's
the desperate one now.
Well,
maybe...
she'll be desperate enough
to come crawling to you.
Errand boy?
She doesn't have to.
- She always has me.
- Oh?
"Has me?" Really?
Wow.
With your weird look,
do you think Marla
will actually like you?
Yuck.
You saw the video, right?
It's forever on the internet.
Besides, you don't have
any stake here,
so why even bother meddling?
Tell me.
I'm not like you in any way.
You're more disgusting because
I never changed how I see Marla
because of the video and photos
of her that you leaked.
They would never determine
her character.
You know, if there was
any mistake Marla made,
it was not seeing the
kind of man you really are.
Ouch.
You chauvinist pig!
- What did you say?
- Cole?!
- Cole, enough!
- Say that again!
- Cole!
- You animal!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- What did you say?
- Cole! Stop it!
Please!
Cut it out!
- Cole! Cole, stop!
- Migo, hold him!
[ANT] Cole!
Enough already!
- Please!
- Cole!
Stop! Fuck you, Cole!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- Cole!
Cole, cut it out!
- Hold him, Migo!
- Cole, come on!
That's enough, Cole!
- What the fuck, Cole?!
- Migo, hold him!
- Please, just stop!
- Migo!
Don't let your emotions
take over!
Stop it!
Okay, girls,
so my only request is at least
thirty minutes of peace
and quiet.
Just silence and serenity,
thirty minutes, okay?
Starting...
now.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
This is okay, too...
not doing anything at all.
No homework, no projects.
No, it's not.
But I guess this is
better than that
goddamn school right now.
I know, right?
Shh.
I have an idea!
[MARLA EXHALES SHARPLY]
Let's just play
Spirit of the Glass.
Huh?
That's your great idea?
- But you're afraid of ghosts.
- So, what?
The high school experience
won't be complete
without someone
getting possessed.
- Oh!
- Right?
Want to see someone
who's possessed?
- Isobel's right here beside me.
- [CHUCKLES]
Yeah, she is!
[CHUCKLING]
Excuse me.
I'm not possessed.
I'm just a witch bitch.
Oh.
She's owning it!
I'm so proud of you!
[CHUCKLES]
You know, I really like your
energy today.
You're so calm!
[CHUCKLING]
Hey, Isobel,
don't tell me
you're really possessed.
[NYX CHUCKLING]
Stop.
I'm not trying to do
something impulsive.
Every time I do,
it always just backfires.
Oh, wow!
You're so self-aware.
[GROANS] Girls!
I asked for just thirty minutes
of peace and quiet.
You couldn't even give me five!
[SIGHS]
Sorry, did we already start?
- A while back.
- Oh, sorry.
I thought thirty minutes.
But, alright.
I just want to know something.
So...
- Who was the masked man?
- Hmm?
- Was it Warren?
- [GIGGLES]
Hold tight.
There.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[NYX] Actually...
it was Ant.
Huh?
- Ant, really?
- M-mmh.
[NYX] That was Ant.
He helped us.
I'm sorry.
Truly, deeply,
for treating your heart
like it was mine to risk.
I admit, I was just
performing for the boys.
What I was doing was wrong.
I knew from the very beginning
you could get hurt
in the process.
And what happened has been
bothering me for months,
and that kind of selfishness
leaves a mark.
So, I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
Don't cry, or I'll hit you.
I'm not crying.
Actually, he also helped me
make the...
lie detector machine, and...
the tickling was his idea.
I don't know about that gay!
Maybe it's his fetish!
- It's insane.
- [CHUCKLING]
Let's just clear one thing.
You forgave him, but not us.
Sure.
I'm not forcing you all to
forgive him right away...
But, hey, you!
Don't forget.
You outed him.
I know.
Do I feel bad?
Yes.
Do I regret it?
No.
Would I apologize?
Also no.
Really?
Well...
he did help us with our
science fair project.
Fine, maybe if he
apologizes first.
As Mark Twain said,
"Forgiveness is the fragrance
the violet sheds
on the heel that
has crushed it."
- Yes...
- Yes.
Whatever that means.
Hey.
Naughty ladies,
something's vibrating?
- [CHUCKLING]
- Oh.
- I said no phones!
- Someone's calling.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's Ant...
- You better not say, "Nug-nug."
- Hey!
- Nug-nug!
- [CHUCKLING]
Kidding! Hey, bestie!
Hello?
Bestie?
So loud!
What?!
Why? What happened?
What happened?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Nyx?
Hey?
[MUSIC STOPS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MARLA] Ant?
- [NYX] Oh, my God!
Ant, what happened?
What did they do to you?
Oh, my God!
We have to call the police.
we have to call the police!
- Nyx.
- Where are your phones?
Nyx!
Relax, I'm all right.
- I'm okay, Nyx.
- Police...
[NYX] Call the police.
[ANT] I'm fine.
Warren's parents
already called the police,
okay?
I've already talked
to them, and...
I doubt they can do anything.
Cole's dad is well-connected.
[GRUNTS]
That damned bastard Cole.
That whole gang of theirs?
The Kings of SOSH?
They're all king of shits!
King shits, all of them.
Those damn fucking assholes,
full of pig shit!
Ant, I'm really sorry.
I am really, really sorry.
Cole's an asshole,
and you're right.
Dad will just cover this up.
April.
Don't sweat it.
This isn't your fault.
I'll recover, but...
Warren...
- Warren?
- What?
Warren?
Why? What happened?
What about Warren?
[MARLA] What happened?
Ant! What happened?
Why was Warren there?
What was he doing there?
How did he get there, Ant?
Ant, speak up!
Shhh.
[ANT] Marla, Warren tried
to save me from Cole.
But he's going
to be okay, right?
- Ant...
- [ANT] I'm sorry, but...
- he's in a state of coma.
- [DAPHNE GASPS]
[ANT] There's also a chance
that he'd get paralyzed.
- Oh, no.
- My God.
Not like this, no.
No!
- No.
- [ANT] Sorry, guys.
[NYX EXHALES SHARPLY]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
No.
This can't be right.
This can't be happening!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[MARLA] No, it can't be.
It's wrong.
No!
No.
This is wrong.
Warren...
Warren just saved my life.
He's the only guy
who never judged me.
This can't happen, Isobel.
This can't happen.
- No, Marla.
- This can't happen.
[ISOBEL] Marla, stop!
We're not going to tell
a eulogy right now.
He's still alive!
Okay?
You know what we need to do?
You know what we need to do?!
We need to do to them what
they did to Warren and Ant.
Finish it off!
[APRIL] Aren't you tired
of this?
It's becoming a cycle where we
always end up losing.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] No.
No.
Isobel is right.
We need to hit them back!
And we need to hit harder!
Girl, I'm really scared
right now.
Look at Ant.
[NYX] Look at what
they're capable of.
Just look at Ant.
I don't want to live
in fear anymore, Nyx.
[MARLA] Exactly.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We can't let them
have power over us.
What's left to be afraid of?
They've taken everything
from us.
They've hurt the people
we love the most.
I want the satisfaction of
taking everything from them.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
They need to pay for
everything they did to us.
I won't stop until
justice is served.
We need to finish...
what we started.
Are you with me?
We need to do this together!
Yes!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wait, what are you going to do?
First,
we need to gather information
before we strike.
Remember the stargazing party?
I had a moment with Mr. Stalker.
- Mr. Stalker?
- Oh?
Ah.
Sorry, I forgot the name.
But...
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Beer.
I've been drinking a lot--
I've drunk a lot already.
Not enough.
I thought,
you invited me here because--
Do you want to make out with me?
Or do you want me
to take you seriously?
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I saw this coming.
First...
you need to earn my trust
before I give you a chance.
You need to tell me the truth.
Carl?
Pearl?
- Earl.
- Earl!
Earl.
You know why
I don't like people like you?
Why?
Because you're friends
with assholes,
like Cole and Lester.
[ISOBEL] You're just
like one of them.
I'm not even friends
with those guys!
I'm just forced to.
Especially that Lester?
I actually do his homework
for him.
Why do you let them bully you?
He's the principal's son.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What about it?
Well, he takes so much
after his mom.
You can trust me, Earl.
[ISOBEL] Spill it out.
This stays between us, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Promise.
- Promise?
- Mm-hmm.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Principal Mckenna...
is corrupt.
Corrupt? [GASPS]
[EARL] Mm-hmm.
- Oh, my...
- Yeah.
As you know...
a big chunk of
the school budget...
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
comes from government funding...
and alumni donations, right?
Mm-hmm.
Do you know of the new building?
Hm?
The Rosalind Franklin
Laboratory.
A ghost company
of the husband...
of Principal Mckenna
handled its construction.
And that's just
the tip of the iceberg.
Interesting.
Tell me more.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Isobel, this is perfect.
Now, April, you're next.
You know what to do.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I just need more time to
download everything.
Hurry up.
Damn!
Guys, SOS!
The principal is coming,
let's go!
Wait, we haven't found any
incriminating evidence yet.
Oh no, just do it later!
- Just come back for it!
- No!
Now that we're already here,
we might as well
finish everything!
- [NYX] Oh, my God!
- [MARLA] She's close!
- I can hear her voice already.
- It's almost done.
- Quiet.
- Shit.
Is that Lucy Pearl?
Idiot. Lucifer.
Oh, you're not up to date.
Lucy Pearl is Lucifer's wife.
- Ah.
- Ha!
- Can you finish that today?
- Almost there, girl.
- Please finish it today.
- Lord...
- Okay, got it. Let's go.
- There!
- Shit.
- We should've gone earlier!
- This is it, go!
- Go, go, go!
Oh, my God!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Lester?
I need you to
do something for me.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Nyx?
You're next.
It's so hard being the visual
of this girl group.
- Migosky...
- [MIGO YELPS]
Nyx!
[BLOWS SHARPLY]
- [NYX CHUCKLES]
- [MIGO] Hi.
- Hi, Nyx!
- Hi, Migosky.
I missed you.
Hm?
You are very,
very beautiful today.
Oh, thank you so much.
That's my default.
[MIGO CHUCKLES]
- By the way...
- Mm?
[MIGO] What brings you here?
- [MIGO CHUCKLES]
- [NYX EXHALES SHARPLY]
Okay, Nyx, I see you.
You can just tell me
if you want to kiss me again.
[CHUCKLES] Honestly, Nyx,
I got to admit it to you,
I really feel the same way, and,
- [LIP POPS]
- ever since that day...
I could never forget your lips.
Whoa, really? [CHUCKLES]
Same.
Actually, we can kiss again.
Do you want to?
But not today.
Not today, I'll hit you.
Actually, I'm here because...
No, just wait.
Calm down a bit.
Calm down. How cute.
Such a cutie. Oh, my God.
I have a request for you.
Stay still for a bit.
Listen, I have a simple request,
and I feel that, you can
handle it easily,
Wait a minute.
I need you to remove the...
the cybersecurity you installed
in the profiles of
the Kings of SOSH.
I don't know anything
about that!
- No? Really?
- [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
No, no.
I really don't know.
What a little liar!
April also told me that
only you can do it.
Why don't you just ask her?
Why involve me?
You know,
you don't have to pretend.
She even admitted that
you're really the best hacker.
Maybe, not just in SOSH.
- Really?
- Yes!
You think I'm great?
Huh? Are you okay?
You're having an episode
in the afternoon?
But no, really.
I really think you're great!
We don't have to ask April,
when she can't even
hack the profiles
of the Kings of SOSH, right?
- Yeah.
- You're the only one who could!
Come on!
- Fuck April!
- Oh!
Wow, okay.
- Oh, sorry.
- [NYX GIGGLES]
[SIGHS DEEPLY}
Of course, Nyx.
I didn't just secure their...
accounts.
I also changed
the auth flow that
I know only I could accomplish.
And I'm very sure that...
not even April can hack that.
Oh, wow,
you're really hot when
- you're nerding out.
- Oh, oh.
You're so hot,
even I get hot-headed with you.
Don't you worry, you won't
need Mr. Ramirez.
You won't need
the Kings of SOSH.
You have nothing
to worry about.
[NYX] Here.
Oh! What's this?
Your new nudes?
You asshole.
Oh, sorry.
But, what is this?
It's a leakage...
of all our exams.
So you could pass for
the whole school year.
No more worries,
and you won't need them again.
How did you get this?
Oh!
Aren't you that close
with Lester?
[NYX] Ohhh!
To the M, to the G!
Didn't he ever tell you that
he always gets this
from his mom?
Also known as Principal Mckenna!
How would I know,
when he treats me like
I'm the dumbest guy?!
Give me that!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Your side profile looks good.
[NYX] Right?
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, hi, Marla!
I'm glad that you're back.
I'm so sorry for
what happened to you.
But, I just want you
to know that
I believe you.
Thank you so much.
- Okay, see you around.
- Thank you, I appreciate it.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know what, sometimes,
ranking doesn't even
mean anything,
Right?
Stop acting like
the main character.
Maybe use your brain.
[DAPHNE] Hey,
you ugly blabbermouths!
Couldn't you just
shut up for once?
That's why your rankings
are all so low!
- Hey, you!
- Daphne.
- I'll squash your face!
- Daphne!
Let's not make a scene.
Oh, girl.
Whether or not
there's a scene, this is it!
We are the main characters.
We're the primetime stars!
- Slay, girls!
- Welcome back, Marla.
Would you want me
to poison them?
Or rebond her hair?
She looks like a scarecrow.
[DAPHNE] How ugly.
That's sweet.
You're all very sweet.
But, I'm okay.
Besides...
you know why I'm here.
I want to watch this.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
[MCKENNA] No!
No!
These are bogus charges!
I did nothing wrong!
No! Please, no!
- Just explain at the station!
- Get your hands off me!
What embezzlement?
I'm not corrupt!
No! Get your hands off me!
- Please, ma'am.
- No!
No!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You did this, didn't you?
You did this!
Huh?
You...
You did this!
[MCKENNA GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMS]
That's enough.
Just come with us.
- Lester!
- Mommy!
Hey! Let her go!
- Mom! What happened?
- Lester!
Call your dad, please!
- Dad?
- Yeah, please!
- Come on!
- Wait, where are you going?
- Mommy!
- [MCKENNA SCREAMING]
[MCKENNA] Get your hands off me!
No!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're all insane, aren't you?
I know you're all behind this.
Right?
Huh?
Haven't you learned your lesson?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ISOBEL] Why would we,
man-child?
Didn't we just succeed?
Mind your own business.
[COLE] I just used you
for pleasure.
How sad.
Marla even saw your panty.
[YAWNS]
That's old news, Cole.
Is there nothing new?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, April.
[COLE] A bastard child.
[APRIL GIGGLES]
Sorry.
Yes?
What?
Are you still not afraid of Dad?
[APRIL] What is he going to do?
Beat me up again?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What else is new?
You really never learn, huh?
Just because
you're getting somewhere?
Well...
I know this is your grand plan.
Do you know you're going
against SOSH now?
Huh?
Aren't you afraid, huh?
Not at all.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know this, right?
That SOSH is capable
of protecting its
good name and reputation.
And if the school goes down...
you'll all go down with it.
Cole, can we speed this up?
This is getting so boring.
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
[MARLA] Also...
what makes you think that
we care about the school?
Like I don't even care
if I don't graduate.
The only thing I care about...
is to watch you suffer.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh.
- Suffer?
- Mm-hmm.
[COLE] I'm not scared.
Oh, I'm not trying to scare you.
Well
Okay.
Good luck!
[APRIL GIGGLES]
You're just women.
So why are you the one crying?
- I'm not crying.
- Crybaby.
[MARLA] You're about to.
You look girlier than us
with that foundation.
- What's your shade?
- [GIGGLING]
We don't need your good luck.
But, thanks.
This is not worth our time.
Let's go.
- How boring.
- Bye-bye.
[ISOBEL] You look a bit shorter.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Been here long?
I'm always punctual.
Of course, you are.
Marla...
we really haven't had
the chance to talk since...
you know.
I want to say thank you.
For still believing in me.
For trusting me.
And I'm sorry.
I'm...
I'm so sorry...
for leaking your photos
and ruining your life.
Well, we both know that
Cole can be very convincing.
I'm also at fault here.
I could have said no.
I could have told him that...
what he wanted to do was wrong.
I could have stopped him.
I really, really regret
what I did.
I won't lie.
What you did was shit.
But I also believe that...
if he didn't force you,
he would have ordered
someone else.
Or he would have
done it himself.
I know Cole's been set on
destroying me and our group.
April...
I'm not trying to be the
bigger person here, okay?
But what you did hurt me deeply.
[POIGNANT MUSIC BUILDS]
[MARLA] But I also understand
why you did it.
[SNIFFLES]
[APRIL SOBS]
Marla...
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
[EXHALES]
I don't expect you to
forgive me right away,
[SNIFFLES]
but I really want
to make it up to you
and the girls.
[SNIFFLES]
Because, Marla...
...you're my friend.
[POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[APRIL] You guys
are my only real friends.
[SNIFFLES]
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
[APRIL SNIFFLES]
[POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES, SNIFFLES]
[EXHALES]
Are you fine with
what we'll do to Cole?
[POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
This may sound weird...
but...
I think...
this can be good for Cole
in the long run.
When... [SNIFFLES]
I was exposed for cheating,
my reputation was ruined.
It was worse...
...how dad beat me up then.
But...
since then...
...he totally ignored me.
[POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
He knows there's nothing
I can do
to save my reputation.
So...
I'm already useless
for his reputation.
Cole needs to take
accountability
for what he did
to Ant and Warren.
[POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry for ratting you out.
I already told you...
don't be sorry for doing
the right thing, Marla.
It was all my fault.
[DOOR OPENS]
[NYX] Shockers.
Heart-to-heart talk?
Are there...
changes in Warren's progress?
You know girls...
let's just pray
to the Lord Almighty
for Warren's fast recovery.
Okay, since we're all
here now...
[LAPTOP FLIPS OPEN]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Here's all the data I collected
when I hacked the boys'
social media accounts.
I was able to recover their
deleted group chat.
[NYX GASPS]
You're the girl!
You know what, April...
so resplendent.
Ooh, resplendent!
And here's the deleted email
Cole sent me
where your nudes are.
We don't need to see that.
[APRIL] Sorry.
So, what are we waiting for?
Let's release
all of that right now!
No.
Timing is everything.
We need to make it big.
We need something
like a spectacle.
So, the school can't deny us.
We should do it at the prom.
Perfect!
I also thought of that!
What a poser.
Is she a devil's advocate?
I think we can also, like,
send it to the police?
Or...
your mom's lawyer?
Well...
I mean look at Warren.
Nothing happened.
Also...
Migo deleted the CCTV
footage from the parking.
He knows,
when they're all caught
in action,
he'd go down, too.
It'll be tough facing dad.
If we're going to do this,
we need to to do it perfectly.
Well...
I can still send evidence
to my mom's lawyer.
But, we're way past the point
of waiting for the police
to do something.
It may even take us years.
I don't want to wait
for a justice system
that moves so slowly.
We need to be deliberate.
We need to be precise.
And we need to make
them feel something.
That's the kind of justice
I want.
[MOUTH CLICKS] Shoot.
Okay, girl.
I agree with you.
So...
now...
Let's prepare for the prom?
Or should I say...
Operation Revenge Prom?
[CHUCKLES] Wow!
I thought of that.
I brainstormed with myself.
With myself.
[CHUCKLES] So redundant!
- Redundant?
- Shh.
Nyx, you're getting worse.
Yeah! Come on.
[NYX] Getting worse?
[APRIL] Bye.
You're not backing out
on the plan, aren't you?
If you really want to know
what I feel...
All I feel is anger.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
And I know that my judgment
might be clouded
because of this,
but, I don't care.
I like it.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't want this feeling...
this anger...
...to go away.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARLA] I'm afraid...
that if I let go of my anger,
I'll just let them go.
Just let them run freely,
and I'll let them get away.
I don't care about the
consequences of our actions.
I just want my revenge.
Good.
No backing out.
I already created
the formula last night.
You mean the paralysis serum?
In theory...
I just combined
neuromuscular blockers
and natural neurotoxins
together.
Oh, and I also added
non-lethal snake venom
just to be sure.
But then again,
in theory,
it's just enough to
make them suffer in agony.
Without...
killing them,
of course.
But I just...
haven't...
tested it yet.
It's just cruel to test
on animals...
right now.
No, no.
We can still test on animals.
And by animals.
I mean the Kings of SOSH.
Oh, Marla...
You're so evil.
I love it.
[SINISTER MUSIC SWELLS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS DARK]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS SOPHISTICATED]
[SOPHISTICATED MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's time to announce
this year's
Prom King and Queen!
Are you, guys, ready?
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Okay, let us start!
This year's Prom King is...
[DRUM ROLL]
No surprise,
Cole Javier!
[APPLAUDING]
[MOUTHS] Ew.
[HOST] Congratulations, Cole.
[MARLA] Ew.
[APPLAUDING]
[HOST] Okay, meanwhile...
This year's Prom Queen is
[DRUM ROLL]
Marla Briones!
[NYX] What? Wait, what?
I mean, you deserve it.
But, why is he your King?
[APPLAUDING]
Hey, go on.
[HOST] Congratulations, Marla!
Isobel, it's up to you.
[APPLAUDING]
[HOST] Once again,
our Prom King and Queen,
and now, may we request
our Royal Couple
to have their first dance.
- [COLE] May I?
- [MARLA CHUCKLES]
My Queen.
Shut up.
Let's just get this over with.
[SLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
You look good.
- Really.
- Thank you.
I wish I could say the same.
[CHUCKLES]
You never cease to amaze me.
Even the results here at prom,
you've manipulated.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
That's more your style.
Okay. Alright.
I'd buy it,
that you really are the Queen...
Queen of playing the victim.
[MARLA] Hmm.
And you're the short,
fragile ego king.
[LAUGHING]
- [LIGHT SMACK]
- [BOTH CHUCKLING]
Babe...
Can we please not fight here?
No, don't call me that.
Disgusting.
[SLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're the one
who made that call sign.
[MARLA] Yuck.
Why are you disgusted?
And why are you angry?
Why so angry?
Is it because...
I outsmarted you?
Huh?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
You think what you did
was smart?
- What did you say?
- [MARLA CHUCKLES]
[MARLA] Don't you remember
all the vile things
you did to me and the girls?
And you almost killed
Ant and Warren.
That idiot Warren,
was minding my business.
Nosy idiot.
He already knows
you're mine, right?
Is he already courting you?
Or...
did something happen already?
Fuck off.
It's none of your concern.
I am not yours.
And I am not anybody's.
Remember that.
Just so you know...
Principal Mckenna
just got out of prison.
So, whatever it is
you're planning...
Whatever it is
you won't succeed.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
You don't know
what we're capable of.
Okay?
Why don't you all
just quit SOSH?
[PAPERS SCATTERING]
- [INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PAPERS SCATTERING]
Really, Marla?
This is it?
Confetti?
Really?
[MARLA] Why don't you
quit SOSH?
Go ahead!
Pick up every little piece
of paper
on that damn floor!
Pick it up!
Every single piece
of paper on the floor,
pick it up!
Every damn piece!
Everything you read
on that paper...
Everything...
is from these filthy boys!
Their filthy mouths!
- [INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [STUDENTS MURMURING]
What'd you call them?!
The Kings of SOSH!
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
They're all perverts.
They got no balls!
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Not edited.
Not fabricated.
Not taken out of context.
That is who they truly are
when no one is watching.
Oh! And not just that.
You can find
every vile comment
of people on the internet
against us.
Go!
Pick them up,
and see for yourselves.
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know...
girls grew up being told
to be careful around strangers.
But, nobody told us
that sometimes,
the ones that'll ruin us...
...are those who are
closest to us.
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
And before you say...
"not all boys,"
then...
if you're one of those
who didn't do anything
while they were doing all these,
those who gave "haha" reacts,
those who commented with emojis,
and those who sent pictures
to your friends,
to your group chats,
and specially those who
protected these people,
and all your friends,
after knowing what they did...
...you're part of that.
You're one of them.
Because silence...
Silence is not innocence!
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
And that goes out
to this very school.
This very school was
supposed to protect us,
was supposed to keep us safe.
I know you're angry.
Good!
Feel exposed?
Feel humiliated?
Embarrassed?
That tiny panic in your chest?
Us, girls, have to live
with that
every damn day of our lives!
So as you pick up those
tiny pieces on the floor,
know that you are also
picking up a piece of our pain!
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Can I just say something?
Let's give them a big hand.
- [APPLAUDING]
- Wooh!
I can't hear you, guys.
Please?
Give them a big hand.
[APPLAUDING, CHEERING]
I agree with Marla.
This school...
is supposed to be
our safe space.
And we all know,
its students are handpicked
from the entire country
and selected to study here
at SOSH.
And I'm sorry
that all of you suddenly...
had to realize that...
those who study here...
...are not perfect,
like these ones.
Yes.
Especially these ones.
But...
let's not pretend that
this school...
doesn't destroy people.
You think people survive
that without
finding ways to cope?
Some of you here,
resort to drinking.
- [MIGO Right!
- [LESTER] Yes!
Others, they mentally breakdown.
- Yeah!
- It's true!
So what if we had
that group chat?
A private space
where we said stupid things.
That even if we're smart,
we're all still teenagers.
[CHUCKLES]
That's why...
we've decided that...
everyone who came to this prom
are all invited
to a private vacation
to take place...
at Amanpulo!
[STUDENTS CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- [STUDENT 1] Let's go!
- [WHISTLING]
[COLE] Don't worry, guys!
Wait a minute, wait up.
- Wait!
- Hey! Hey! Wait!
Hold it!
All expenses paid.
[STUDENTS CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- [STUDENT 2] Let's go!
- [STUDENT 3] Let's go!
[WHISTLING, CLAPPING]
[COLE] Let's enjoy, guys!
Damn all the Kings of SOSH!
You know,
we'll just forever be known
as scandal girls.
Whatever.
Those suck-ups.
See.
So cool. Mm.
- [DAPHNE] What's that?
- It's got a zapper!
For what?
- Plan B!
- Oh!
[NYX]
Don't worry, it has a switch.
Bzzt!
- Cool!
- Bzzt!
- Bzzt, bzzt!
- Like this!
Where's Marla and Isobel?
I thought we
were meeting them here.
Oh.
We're at the right place, right?
I'm sure.
Diva!
- Is it really here?
- Hey, it is!
- Just text them.
- Come on, trust me.
For real.
What are you doing?
April,
Marla talked to me.
What are they up to?
April, please listen.
You have to stop
whatever they're planning to do.
Then don't do this, Migo.
Please?
Migo, don't do this.
I know you so well.
I know you--
Isobel made this.
It immobilizes your muscles
for an hour.
It relaxes you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLUB MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [PEOPLE COUGHING]
[PEOPLE COUGHING]
Oh, hey!
Are you okay?
Hey!
[BODY THUDS]
[MCKENNA] What's happening?
[MCKENNA GASPS] This...
this is bad!
[PHONE RINGS, BEEPS]
- Lester?
- [LESTER] Mommy?
- Where the hell are you?!
- [LESTER] I just--
Don't come here anymore.
- [LESTER] Where's Cole?
- Just let Cole be!
Something very bad
is going down here.
- [LESTER] I'll go to you.
- No!
- Just go home!
- [LESTER] Okay.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
See?
I told you
my sleeping bomb works.
[MARLA] Okay, okay,
but we can't brag yet.
We need to look for Cole.
Wait...
Is that Ant?
Shit, I forgot to warn him!
- Ant?
- [ISOBEL] Ant!
Ant.
Ant...
He's not gonna wake up, Marla,
we have to pick him up.
Now.
[MARLA] Let's put him here.
Are you looking for me?
We've been waiting for you.
Just in time.
What the fuck?
Really?
Water gun? That's it, Marla?
[COLE CHUCKLES]
You're just laughing
because you don't know
what this can do.
I know you're dangerous, Isobel.
But,
I know someone who
can't ever hurt me.
My girlfriend.
Right, babe?
You can never hurt me, right?
- Babe?
- Oh, suck it, Cole!
Stop calling me "babe."
You know, that's what
I like about you, so feisty.
You know, Marla,
we could have been
the perfect couple.
We could have created
the cure for cancer together.
Or discovered a second Earth.
We can do all that,
just come back to me,
please, babe?
Let's get back together.
You're nuts.
Shut up, Isobel.
- You're insane!
- You're the one who's nuts!
- You ruined our relationship.
- Oh, you shut up!
Cole, you sound just like
your fucking dad.
[ISOBEL] You know what?
How dare you?!
How dare you!
You fucking approached me!
You used my animosity
against Marla,
just so you could
enable your cheating.
You know what? Fuck you!
You...
you took my photos
without my consent,
when I said no!
Come on, Isobel.
You liked it, didn't you?
You liked it so much.
We went at it
for how many rounds,
was it three...
four?
Five?
Right?
Damn you.
I regret every second of it.
Every chance you had with me.
I regret making myself small
for a boy like you.
I regret hurting Marla.
You know what I don't regret?
I'll never regret
ruining your life.
You know,
I can see through you, Isobel.
You're just doing this
to get between me and Marla.
I don't know if you like me
or you like my girlfriend more?
Babe, do you see
what she's doing?
She wants to get
between us, babe.
She just wants us to fight.
- Please?
- Are you stoned?
Can you just forget
that crazy witch?
- Look at her.
- What did you just snort?
We can still go to Harvard
together, babe, please?
- Let's get back together.
- I'd still be better than you.
Come on.
Please, babe.
Do you actually think
that I would get back
together with you,
despite everything you did?
You didn't even feel bad
when you released my video
that you recorded
without my consent!
[LAUGHING]
[COLE] You know what's funny,
Marla, huh?
What?
I still love you.
I really, really love you.
- [SCOFFS]
- [MARLA] It is funny.
You know at first,
I just approached you, Marla,
and courted you
because I wanted
to avenge April.
But, you made me
fall in love with you.
There, I totally forgot.
But, I was genuine to you,
Marla. I really loved you.
I love you so much.
What?
So you're telling me,
you planned this
from the beginning?
Yes...
No?
Yes... No... No.
[COLE STAMMERS]
I can't think straight
with you, Marla.
It wasn't really part of the
plan to fall in love with you.
[SCOFFS] Wow.
[COLE] But, I truly,
madly fell in love with you.
Wait.
You know Bayes' Theorem.
Well, I know you do.
You're Marla Briones.
You're smart.
You know,
my prior belief of you
is that you're a very caring
and loving person, Marla.
That's what I liked about you.
And as time goes by,
I slowly discovered
how very selfish
and self-centered
you are, Marla.
You didn't let me win once,
even just one term,
just one term, Marla!
You still haven't moved on
from that?
- Yes!
- So, that made you
change your mind about me?
What's the posterior, huh?
That the evidence
kept supporting my suspicion.
You're selfish.
You're self-centered.
You don't even care
that I failed
just so you could be
top one, Marla.
What kind of
a girlfriend are you?
a boyfriend are you?
I can apply the
Bayes' Theorem to you, too.
'Cause you're not the
same person I fell in love with.
I'm done.
Oh, my god,
can we just do
what we came here to do?
Earl?
You can go.
Go.
You tricked me, Isobel.
You just used me.
It's because you're gullible.
You know what gullible is?
You don't know me.
I really hate it when people
make me look stupid.
Really?
But, you really are an idiot,
ever since.
Acting like a loyal pet
to Cole and Lester.
And now,
you're Lester's substitute.
Say what you want to say.
If I'm a pet,
then I bite.
Really?
- Yes!
- [GRUNTS]
- Isobel!
- [COLE] Earl!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[MARLA] Isobel, go!
[COLE] Fight her, Earl.
Go, go! Go!
Keep going!
Hey.
Don't you dare move.
[ISOBEL, EARL GRUNTING]
[MARLA] Isobel!
- [KICK LANDS]
- [EARL] Aah!
Ouch! Damn it!
[GROANING]
What's that, Isobel?!
[SCREAMING]
What's that?
Damn you!
Fuck!
[EARL SCREAMING IN AGONY]
[ISOBEL] Guess what?
I bite harder!
[MARLA] Hey!
[COLE] Isobel, please...
Put it down, you might
kill me, please?
Shit.
- Marla...
- Marla, Isobel,
stop it, please!
- Sorry, sorry, girl...
- What are you doing?
- I'm very sorry, girl.
- Please drop it!
[NYX] Sorry, girl.
[ISOBEL]
You stupid fucking girl,
- why are yo--
- Stop!
- [DAPHNE] Marla, please...
- April, get out. Go!
- No!
- [ISOBEL] Why now?
Sorry, girl, you're not the only
ones with a plan.
[DAPHNE]
Marla, drop the gun, please.
Marla, this is not right.
- Marla.
- No!
- We can still save him, Marla.
- No, that's enough, Marla!
- Don't drop the damn gun.
Isobel, stop!
- No!
Alright.
[NYX] Cole!
- [DAPHNE] Cole!
- You want this, right?
[APRIL] Cole, stop.
- Killing?
- Drop it, Cole.
You drop that first.
- [APRIL] Cole... no.
- I will stab her.
- Cole, please
- I will kill her.
[NYX] Marla, think about April!
- Marla, please.
- What now, Marla?!
Drop it!
- Marla...
- Marla.
- Marla, it's April.
- No.
- [DAPHNE] April...
- This is all your fault.
Cole, drop it.
- You should've avoided them.
- [MARLA] Let her go, now!
- Drop it.
- Enough, please!
[COLE] Go on!
- Marla, I will kill her!
- [MARLA] No!
[DAPHNE] Drop it!
I will count to three!
One.
- Two.
- [KNIFE WHOOSHES]
- [DAPHNE] Cole!
- Cole!
You believe me now?
Marla, please...
- Drop it now.
- Drop your gun.
Marla, just let it go, please.
You won't do it?
Drop your gun!
I'll do it, damn you!
[APRIL] Cole, enough,
please, Cole, stop it.
[ISOBEL] Damn it.
- [MARLA] Let her go.
- [DAPHNE] Oh, my...
- [THUDS]
- [GLASS CLATTERS]
- Daphne...
- What now?
- [GRUNTS]
- Fuck!
- [NYX] Damn!
- [MARLA] Cole!
Stop!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [ISOBEL GRUNTS]
[MARLA] You animal!
Marla!
- Stop, Cole!
- Fine.
This is what you want, right?
Huh?
You want this, right?
Cole, enough, please...
If I won't get to the top,
then I'll kill you, Marla.
Cole, stop.
[MARLA COUGHS]
[MARLA PANTS]
[COLE] What's this?
[APRIL] Marla, just let it go.
- Stop, Marla...
- [COLE] Marla.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Marla!
[DAPHNE] Marla, enough!
[APRIL] Marla.
[COLE GRUNTS]
[ISOBEL] Go, Marla.
Go!
- [APRIL] Marla, stop.
- [DAPHNE] Marla, that's enough.
[ISOBEL] Go, Marla!
[APRIL] Marla!
You ruined my life.
You ruined
everything in my life.
Fuck you.
You ruined my life.
I'll kill you!
[MARLA SCREAMS]
- [DAPHNE] Marla!
- [APRIL] Marla, stop!
- [NYX] Marla!
- [BLOW LANDS]
[APRIL] Marla!
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOW LANDS]
- [MARLA GRUNTS]
- Marla, that's enough...
- Marla...
- [ISOBEL] Go, Marla! Do it!
Finish it!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUNDER CRASHING, RUMBLING]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[APRIL] Marla, please.
[ISOBEL] Go, Marla!
[APRIL CRYING] Marla, stop...
Marla, please...
[ISOBEL] End it.
- [COLE WHIMPERING]
- [MARLA BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[COLE WHIMPERS]
[COLE COUGHING,
GASPING FOR AIR]
[COLE WHEEZING]
[COLE COUGHING]
[COLE] Please...
[COLE GRUNTS, COUGHS]
Marla...
- [APRIL] Marla, please don't.
- [DAPHNE] No, Marla...
Please, don't.
[CRYING]
Marla, please don't.
- [ISOBEL] Finish it.
-I'm begging you, Marla, please.
[APRIL] I'm begging you.
April. April, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- [MARLA] Fuck you.
[COLE] My baby sister, please...
please forgive me...
Marla...
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [INDISTINCT WHISPERS]
[INAUDIBLE]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[BODY THUDS]
[CRYING]
[BRASS KNUCKLES CLINK]
- [SNIFFLES]
- [WATER GUN THUDS]
[WHIMPERING]
You said... [SNIFFLES]
we'll get our justice tonight.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you trust me?
I do.
[SNIFFLING]
We got our revenge.
We got our justice.
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING
IN DISTANCE]
- [FLOODLIGHTS CLICKING]
- [POLICE SIRENS WAILING]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FLOODLIGHTS CLICK]
[MARLA]
They say there's a fine line
between genius and insanity.
But when your life
is on the line,
are you a genius
for surviving?
Or a madwoman for fighting
to the death?
No matter how smart you are,
when it comes to love,
it doesn't give you
the right data,
the right facts.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
When an experiment fails,
you have to review the steps
and figure out what went wrong.
At this point...
all I can think about is...
where did I go wrong?
Was it by loving
the wrong person?
Or by taking justice
into our own hands?
Being a genius is a dream.
But, madness?
Madness is a weapon.
It's the kind of madness
that only happens
when you stop caring about
what the world thinks.
It's the wide-eyed clarity
of realizing
that the same brilliant minds
that could cure a disease
could just as easily
engineer a nightmare.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
There's a fine line
between genius and insanity.
And when you've
crossed that line,
there is no turning back.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]